<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="pref_volume_unit_entries">
        <item>Centimetres and Litres</item>
        <item>Inches and Imperial Gallons</item>
        <item>Inches and US Gallons</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pref_volume_unit_values">
        <item>metric</item>
        <item>imperial</item>
        <item>us</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pref_dosage_unit_entries">
        <item>mg/L</item>
        <item>ppm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pref_dosage_unit_values">
        <item>mgl</item>
        <item>ppm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tank_options">
        <item>Heated</item>
        <item>Plants</item>
        <item>Planted</item>
        <item>Seeded</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="plant_options">
        <item>No Plants</item>
        <item>Lightly Planted</item>
        <item>Heavily Planted</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tank_stage">
        <item>Not Started</item>
        <item>Cycling &lt;Ammonia&gt;</item>
        <item>Cycling &lt;Nitrite&gt;</item>
        <item>Cycling &lt;Nitrate&gt;</item>
        <item>Cycled</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chart_labels">
        <item>Ammonia</item>
        <item>Nitrite</item>
        <item>Nitrate</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="unit_options">
        <item>Metric</item>
        <item>Imperial</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dose_unit_options">
        <item>mg/L</item>
        <item>ppm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="volume_unit_options">
        <item>Litres</item>
        <item>Imp. Gallons</item>
        <item>US Gallons</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_item_headers">
        <item>Essential</item>
        <item>Optional</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="info_item_parents">
        <item>An Aquarium Tank (with Filter, Filter media etc.)</item>
        <item>An Ammonia Source</item>
        <item>A Water Testing Kit</item>
        <item>A Water Siphon/Gravel Cleaner</item>
        <item>A Large Bucket</item>
        <item>A Towel</item>
        <item>Water Conditioner/Dechlorinator</item>
        <item>Syringe/Pipette/Dropper</item>
        <item>Cleaned Substrate</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_item_parents_optional">
        <item>Plants</item>
        <item>Decorations</item>
        <item>Heater</item>
        <item>Seed Material</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_item_children">
        <item>Ammonia sources typically include chemical (i.e. household cleaning Ammonia) and
            organic (i.e. ammonia naturally produced by decaying shrimp, or as a waste product).
            \n\nChemical ammonia is recommended as it provides greater control over dosage
        levels. It is also less likely to encourage "bacterial blooms" during the cycle.
            \n\nIf using store-bought ammonia, check to make sure it does not contain any surfactants
        or fragrances. Check the ingredients label if unsure. The ammonia should not form bubbles or
        foam when shaken.</item>
        <item>
            Water Testing Kits often come as either packs of paper strips or as liquid test kits.
            \n\nLiquid tests kits are recommended as they are more accurate than paper strips.
        </item>
        <item>
            In addition to cleaning substrate, water siphons make water changes substantially easier.
        </item>
        <item>
            As with water siphons, a simple bucket is very useful for conducting water changes. It
            can also be a helpful place to store items related to the aquarium.\n\nIt is recommended
            any bucket used for an aquarium is not used for other tasks (i.e. cleaning) because of
            the risk of contaminating the aquarium with cleaning products.
        </item>
        <item>
            Water Conditioner removes chlorine and chloramines from tap water.\n\nBoth these chemicals
            are toxic to fish and cycling bacteria.
        </item>
        <item>
            Substrate is the stuff that lines the aquarium floor; examples include gravel, sand or
            soil.\n\nTo clean substrate, place it inside a bucket and fill the bucket with water.
            Once the substrate has settled to the bottom, tip out the water.\n\nRepeat the process
            until the water runs clear.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_item_child_optional">
        <item>
            In addition to their aesthetic effects, plants can help speed up or even replace a fishless
            cycle. Plants use ammonia, nitrite and nitrate as a food source, which reduces the load
            on the bacteria in the aquarium.\n\nIf present in a high enough concentration, a \"silent
            cycle\" may take place. This is where the ammonia produced by the tank\'s wildlife is low
            enough that it can be absorbed completely by the plants.
        </item>
        <item>
            Bacteria grow on aquarium surfaces. This mostly takes place inside the filter, but decorations
            will also host some bacteria.
        </item>
        <item>
            Seed material can drastically reduce the time it takes to cycle a new tank.\n\nSeed material
            consists of taking an item from an established, cycled tank (i.e. a piece of filter media)
            and introducing it to the new tank. The bacteria present will begin to multiply immediately
            under the right conditions.\n\nKeep in mind that it is also possible to transmit pathogens
            in this way, so ensure the seeding tank is healthy.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ammonia_doses">
        <item>1^1</item>
        <item>2^1</item>
        <item>3^1 (Recommended)</item>
        <item>4^1</item>
        <item>5^1</item>
        <item>6^1</item>
        <item>7^1</item>
        <item>8^1</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>